Aleksandr Khozhainov

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACTS

+38 068 124 24 77

Telegram: @Aleksandr Khozhainov Email: khozhainov.aleksandr@gmail.com

Skype: Aleksandr Khozhainov Linkedin: aleksandr-khozhainov GitHub: khozhainov-aleksandr

My portfolio: https://khozhainov-aleksandr.github.io/

CodeWars: Aleksandr Khozhainov

Odesa, Ukraine

Ready to work remotely.

SUMMARY

I have experience in a startup (7 months) as an HTML coder and JS developer (worked in the office). I had full-time development education in Mate Academy for 4 months, 2 higher educations, several years of work at sea in English within international crews, 4 years of work as a 3rd mate (it's like assistant of captain). Now I'm Software Developer working with JavaScript, Typescript, React and I open to learn other libraries and frameworks Vue / Angular / React Native.

FRONTEND SKILLS

- Typescript, JavaScript (ES2015 2019)
- React, Redux
- HTML5, CSS3, Sass (SCSS), BEM, Bootstrap
- Fetch, REST API, Web sockets
- Photoshop, Figma
- Git/Github, VS Code, WebStorm, Chrome Developer Tools (incl. React), NPM, Webpack, Trello
- Algorithms: Solved 155 algorithmic tasks
- Basic OOP understanding
- English: Upper-Intermediate

EXPERIENCE

My training projects.

Technologies: JavaScript, React, Typescript, HTML, CSS, BEM

See some of my projects at:

Landing page "Eco Cosmetics"

- <u>Demo</u>: <u>https://tinyurl.com/Project-Eco-Cosmetics</u>
- <u>GitHub Code</u>: <u>https://tinyurl.com/GitHub-Eco-Cosmetics</u>

Landing page "My BiKE"

- <u>Demo:</u> https://tinyurl.com/Project-MyBiKE
- <u>GitHub Code:</u> <u>https://tinyurl.com/GitHub-MyBiKE</u>

Landing page "Netcliks"

- Demo: https://tinyurl.com/Project-Netcliks
- GitHub Code: https://tinyurl.com/GitHub-Netcliks

Landing page "Run Smart"

- <u>Demo</u>: <u>https://tinyurl.com/Project-Run-Smart</u>
- <u>GitHub Code</u>: https://tinyurl.com/GitHub-Run-Smart

Landing page "Uber"

- Demo: https://tinyurl.com/Project-Uber
- <u>GitHub Code</u>: <u>https://tinyurl.com/GitHub-Uber</u>

Landing page "V Klinik"

- <u>Demo</u>: <u>https://tinyurl.com/Project-VKlinik</u>
- GitHub Code: https://tinyurl.com/GitHub-VKlinik

Landing page "Active Box"

- <u>Demo</u>: <u>https://tinyurl.com/Project-Active-Box</u>
- <u>GitHub Code</u>: https://tinyurl.com/GitHub-Active-Box

WORK EXPERIENCE

Company: Nordic Hamburg

Working time in the company: Apr 2016 - Jan 2022

- Position: 'Able Bodied Seaman (AB)' and '3rd Mate'
- Work area: World Wide
- Work in mixed crews

Company: Marlow Navigation Ukraine

Working time in the company: Nov 2010 - Feb 2016

- Position: 'Ordinary Seaman (OS)' and 'Able Bodied Seaman (AB)'
- Work area: World Wide
- Work in mixed crews

EDUCATION

Institution: Odessa National Maritime Academy Qualification and Degree: Sea navigator | Master Dates Attended: 2011 - 2017

Institution: Odessa National Academy Food Technology

Qualification and Degree: Restaurant and hotel business manager | Bachelor

Dates Attended: 2005 - 2010

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

• Frontend course at Mate academy (Git, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, React, Web)

• Hillel: Front-End Pro

• Hillel: Front-End Basic

HTML Academy

Udemy: WEB-developer

• Udemy: Learn to Program in Javascript: Beginner to Pro.

• Sololearn: HTML Fundamentals course

• Sololearn: CSS Fundamentals course

• Sololearn: JavaScript Fundamentals course

Learn.javascript.ru (JavaScript)

Reactjs.org

• CodeWars: Algorithmic tasks

• Book: You Don't Know JS - Kyle Simpson

• Book: JavaScript: The Definitive Guide - David Flanagan

none